<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vighnesh Tamse | DataEnthu</title>
    <link>https://vighneshtamse.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Vighnesh Tamse | DataEnthu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 15:02:07 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://vighneshtamse.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Basic Pytorch Functions</title>
      <link>https://vighneshtamse.github.io/post/basic-pytorch-functions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 12:39:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vighneshtamse.github.io/post/basic-pytorch-functions/</guid>
      <description>Basic Pytorch Tensor Functions Pytorch is a python based scientific computing package which is replacement for Numpy to use the power of GPUs and also provides maximum flexibility and speed. We will now look at 5 of the many interesting pytorch functions in this section.
 torch.from_numpy(ndarray) torch.argmax(input) torch.unsqueeze(input, dim) torch.mm(input, mat2, out=None) torch.pow(input, exponent, out=None)  # Import torch and other required modules import torch import jovian import numpy as np &amp;lt;IPython.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://vighneshtamse.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vighneshtamse.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Pursuing Post Graduate Program in Data Science from Praxis Business School, Bangalore.
Interested in: Machine Learning | Natural Language Processing | Deep Learning
Know about me: Previously I have worked with Capgemini as an Associate Consultant for 2 years and 10 months. During my stint at Capgemini, I heard a lot about the Data Science field and how interesting it is, did a bit research about this field and hence decided to pursue my career in Data Science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding ResNet</title>
      <link>https://vighneshtamse.github.io/post/understanding-resnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 19:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vighneshtamse.github.io/post/understanding-resnet/</guid>
      <description>Deep Residual Learning for Image Recognition (ResNet) In this section we will try to understand some basic concepts related to ResNet architecture, why is it better than VGG Net, its working and its advantages.
Before trying to understand what ResNet is, first lets try to understand in short what is VGG Net and why ResNet is better than VGG Net.
Understanding VGG Net (VGG 16): VGG stands for Visual Geometry Group at Oxford University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Convolutional Neural Networks (CNN)</title>
      <link>https://vighneshtamse.github.io/post/understanding-cnn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 19:58:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vighneshtamse.github.io/post/understanding-cnn/</guid>
      <description>Understanding Convolutional Neural Networks (CNN or ConvNet) Ever wondered how does a computer understands whether an image of a dog is actually a dog? Or how does it know whether the nose of the dog is actually a nose? Well it all starts with a Convolutional Neural Network.
In this section we would understand the following things in order to understand CNNs:
 How a computer reads an image? Why don&amp;rsquo;t we use Fully Connected Neural Networks for Image Recognition?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>